attitude.co.uk 2012-05-01

# Vitality Publishing | Privacy Policy

For the purpose of this statement ‘Website’ refers to the site that you are accessing this Privacy Policy from. 

Last Updated and Effective from: 30/Aug/2010 

Your privacy and trust are very important to Vitality Publishing. This Privacy Policy describes the information that we collect from you, how we collect this, and what we do with it after we collect it. By using the Website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

Please Note: Vitality Publishing reserves the right to make changes to the Privacy Policy at any time. The latest version will always be available from a link on the Website. 

You may be able to access third party websites directly from the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply when you access third party websites. 

**Information We Collect and How We Use It**

When you place an order, or use any online form on our website we will ask for your name and other information such as your postal address, e-mail address, telephone number and your credit card number and expiry date or bank account details etc to allow us to process your request. Only relevant information will be used by us, our agents and sub-contractors to facilitate the service you have requested and potentially communicate with you on any concerns arising to the provision of the service in general. 

We use analytic and reporting technologies to record and collect non-personal information from you. This information, such as your browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system, and your Internet protocol (IP) Address, cannot be easily used to personally identify you. Vitality Publishing reserves the right to use partners, who may use web beacons and cookies to help manage, monitor and optimise our Website to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising, communications and how visitors use the Website. 

**How Is My Personal Information Protected?**

Whenever we obtain your personal information, we use commercially reasonable efforts to protect it from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, we are not insurers of the security of your personal information. Accordingly, we assume no liability for any disclosure of data due to errors in transmission, unauthorised third party access or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control. 

**Website Content.**

The content that you store, post, or transmit on or through the Website, such as forum postings or images, may be accessed by other users, including people that you do not know. We are not responsible for the actions of others. Therefore, you should use care in communicating with other users and only disclose your personal information to other users that you know to be trustworthy. You should not assume that your content will be kept private. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Children Under 13**

The Website is intended for users ages 13 and older. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13. In some instances a child of 13 or under can use the Website but with the authority of a parent or legal guardian. 

**Children Aged 13 to 17**

Prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 can only use the Website under their parents or legal guardian's supervision. If you are between the ages of 13 and 17, you, your parent, or your legal guardian may request that we deactivate your use on areas of the Website that require personal information. 

**Disclosure of Information to Successors**

We may disclose your personal information to any successor-in-interest of ours, such as a company that acquires us. In the event Vitality Publishing goes through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by or with another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Disclosure of Information to Unaffiliated Third Parties.**

We may disclose your personal information to prevent an emergency, to prevent harm to others, to respond to legal requirements, to protect or enforce our rights and policies, to protect or enforce the rights of a third party, or as required or permitted by law (including, without limitation, to comply with a subpoena or court order).
